Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 2, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Fallacy of Machine Hour Restrictions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Author: Henry Pope Jr.
- Box: 2, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Employees Insurance Program, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Author: Bechtel Corporation
  - Item 2: Hospital-Medical Conversion Policies, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Box: 2, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Capital City News Bureau Newspaper Clippings, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Author: Capital City News Bureau
- Box: 2, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Agreement and Contract, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Author: Beech-Nut Packing Company
  - Item 2: Agreement and Contract, 1957; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Agreement and Contract, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Agreement and Contract, 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Agreement and Contract, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Agreement and Contract, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Agreement and Contract, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Box: 2, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Benefit Schedule By-Laws and Rules for Administration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Author: Behr-Manning Welfare Association
- Box: 2, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Techincal Library, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Author: Bell Aerosystems Company
  - Item 2: Fields of Interest, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Box: 2, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Project Total, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Company Information Sheet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Box: 2, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Problems of Federal Retirees, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Author: Bell Aerospace Corporation
  - Item 2: Let's Look at Your Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Primary Effects on Employment of Shifts in Demand From Domestic to Foreign Products, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Author: Walter S. Salant
  - Item 5: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Author: Bell Aerosystems Corporation
  - Item 6: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Let's Look at Your Future, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: A Simulated Instructional Model for Educating Mentally Retarded Students for Employment in the Hotel-Motel Industry, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Author: Research Coordinating Unit
  - Item 9: Revised Safety Program, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Box: 2, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Bell Labs News, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Author: Bell Telephone Laboratories
    Notes: Vol. 14, No. 48 Dec. 9
  - Item 2: Pioneer News, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Author: Jewett Chapter Telephone Pioneers of America
    Notes: No. 25 Dec. 9
  - Item 3: This Week, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: Nov. 11, 1974
  - Item 4: This Week, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Notes: Dec. 6, 1974
- Box: 2, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: PTM, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Bell Telephone
  - Item 2: Review, 1973; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Pacific Telephone
    Notes: No. 211 Aug. 3, 1973
  - Item 3: Information Bulletin, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: New Jersey Bell
    Notes: No. 46 Dec. 20, 1974
  - Item 4: Report to Management, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 41 Dec. 11, 1974
  - Item 5: Report to Management, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 40 Nov. 27, 1974
  - Item 6: Report to Management, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 36 Oct. 2, 1974
  - Item 7: Report to Management, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 39 Nov. 13, 1974
  - Item 8: Report to Management, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol.2, No. 37 Oct. 17, 1974
  - Item 9: Report to Management, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 2, No. 38 Oct. 31, 1974
  - Item 10: Information Bulletin, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Nov. 22, 1974 No. 42
  - Item 11: Information Bulletin, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: No. 1 Jan. 7, 1975
  - Item 12: C&P Communicator, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: The Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia
    Notes: Vol. 7, No. 8 May 27, 1971
  - Item 13: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 4 Feb. 28, 1975
  - Item 14: Bulletin, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Northwestern Bell
    Notes: Vol. 32, No. 10 May 9, 1975
  - Item 15: Bulletin, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 32, No. 9 April 25, 1975
  - Item 16: Bulletin, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 32, No. 7 Mar. 28, 1975
  - Item 17: Bulletin, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 32, No. 6 Mar. 14, 1975
  - Item 18: Bulletin, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Southern New England Telephone
    Notes: March-April
  - Item 19: Telephone Times, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 15, No. 2 July 16, 1975
  - Item 20: NWB News, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 18 May 21, 1875
  - Item 21: NWB News, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 13 March 7, 1975
  - Item 22: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 15 July 30, 1975
  - Item 23: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 13 July 2, 1975
  - Item 24: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 12 June 18, 1975
  - Item 25: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 14 July 16, 1975
  - Item 26: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 11 June 4, 1975
  - Item 27: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 25 Dec. 17, 1975
  - Item 28: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 24 Dec. 4, 1975
  - Item 29: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 22 Dec. 5, 1975
  - Item 30: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 23 Nov. 19, 1975
  - Item 31: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 20 Oct. 8, 1975
  - Item 32: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No.18 Sept. 10, 1975
  - Item 33: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 9 May 7, 1975
  - Item 34: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 16 August 13, 1975
  - Item 35: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 10 May 21, 1975
  - Item 36: Report to Management, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 17 August 27, 1975
  - Item 37: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 6 March 23, 1977
  - Item 38: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 7 April 8, 1977
  - Item 39: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol.5, No. 8 April 20, 1977
  - Item 40: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 5 March 9, 1977
  - Item 41: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 9 May 5, 1977
  - Item 42: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 23 Nov. 21, 1977
  - Item 43: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 10 May 18, 1977
  - Item 44: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No.10 May 18, 1977
  - Item 45: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 11 June 2, 1977
  - Item 46: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 12 June 15, 1977
  - Item 47: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 14 July 13, 1977
  - Item 48: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 15 July 27, 1977
  - Item 49: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 19 Sept. 23, 1977
  - Item 50: Report to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 2 Jan. 27, 1978
  - Item 51: Repoort to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 14 July 28, 1978
  - Item 52: Telenews, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Illinois Bell Telephone Co.
    Notes: April 7, 1979
  - Item 53: Telenews, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: April 21, 1979
  - Item 54: The Bulletin, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Summer 1978
  - Item 55: Tie Lines, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Michigan Bell
    Notes: Vol. 13, No. 14 Aug. 17, 1977
  - Item 56: Tie Lines, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 13, No. 15 Sept. 1, 1977
  - Item 57: Management Report, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 3 March 16, 1977
  - Item 58: Management Report, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 8 July 26, 1977
  - Item 59: News of Special Interes to MBT People, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 1977
  - Item 60: News of Special Interest to MBT People, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 6, 1977
  - Item 61: News for Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 41 Aug. 29, 1977
  - Item 62: News for Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 33 June 15, 1977
  - Item 63: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 17 Aug. 24, 1977
  - Item 64: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 16 Aug. 10, 1977
  - Item 65: Information Bulletin, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Aug. 8, 1977
  - Item 66: Outlook, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 32 Sept. 16, 1977
  - Item 67: C&P Message Register, 1989; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: C&P Telephone
    Notes: Vol. 23, No. 6 March 21, 1978
  - Item 68: Central, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: South Central Bell
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 4
  - Item 69: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 20 Oct. 6, 1977
  - Item 70: Report to Management, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 22 Nov. 2, 1977
  - Item 71: Report to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 9 May 19, 1978
  - Item 72: Report to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 11 June 14, 1978
  - Item 73: Report to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 13 July 14, 1978
  - Item 74: Telephone Times, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: Southern New England Bell
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 25 June 14, 1978
  - Item 75: Telephone Times, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 24 May 31, 1978
  - Item 76: Telephone Times, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 23 May 17, 1978
  - Item 77: Telephone Times, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 22 May 3, 1978
  - Item 78: Telephone Times, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 21 April 19, 1978
  - Item 79: Telephone Times, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 20 April 5, 1978
  - Item 80: Report to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 6, No. 17 Sept. 26, 1978
  - Item 81: Report to Management, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Notes: Vol. 16, No. 18 Oct. 2, 1978
- Box: 2, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Look at the Bell System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Author: Bell Telephone System
  - Item 2: The Telephone in America, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: The Magic of Your Telephone, 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Box: 2, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: A Plan of Group Insurance, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Author: Bellingham, Washington
- Box: 2, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Standards, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Author: Bendix Aviation Corp.
    Notes: April 20, 1948
  - Item 2: Training Department, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Tests, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: For Aerospace Engineering and Scientific CareersThe Bendix Corporation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: You and Your Job, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: Complaint Record, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Box: 2, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance for Employees Paid on an Hourly Basis, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Box: 2, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Automation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Author: Malcolm P. Ferguson
  - Item 2: The Village We Can't Do Without, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Author: Wesley Price
    Notes: Reprint from March 3, 1951 The Saturday Evening Post
  - Item 3: Automation, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Notes: Nov. 29, 1956
- Box: 2, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Representation of Employees in Plants of the Bethlehem Shipbuilding Corp., Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Author: Bethlehem Shipbuilding Corp.
    Notes: March 1, 1923
- Box: 2, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: People 'N Steel, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
    Author: Lackawanna Plant
    Notes: May 31, 1977
- Box: 2, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: A Good Way of Life, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Author: Bibb Manufacturing Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Bibb Family, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Box: 2, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Brass Tacks, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Author: Bigelow Sanford Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Bird & Son Inc. Suggestin Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
    Author: Bird & Son Inc.
  - Item 2: Bird & Son Inc. Suggestion Plan, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 3: Bird & Son Inc. Suggestion Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Box: 2, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: This Question Must Be Answered!, Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Author: Bituminous Coal Operators Association
  - Item 2: For Immediate Release, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Notes: April 3, 1956
- Box: 2, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Things You Will Want to Know About Black and Decker, Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Author: Black and Decker Mfg. Co.
  - Item 2: Things You Will Want to Know About Black & Decker Quality Power Tools, Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Box: 2, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Outline of Principal Features, Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Author: Blaw-Knox Co.
- Box: 2, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Blaw-Knox Co., Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Box: 2, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: A Trip Through Blue Swan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Author: Blue Swan Mills
- Box: 2, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Boeing News, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Author: Boeing
    Notes: Vol. 37, No. 22 June 1, 1978
  - Item 2: Boeing News, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Notes: Vol. 37, No. 21 May 25, 1978
  - Item 3: Boeing News, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Notes: Vol. 37, No. 20 May 18, 1978
- Box: 2, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Changing Pattern of Executive Compensation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Author: Booz Allen & Hamilton Management Consultants
  - Item 2: Teamwork in Business Management, Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Box: 2, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Operators Manual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Author: Boston and Maine Transportation Co.
- Box: 2, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Boston Library Serves Labor Unions, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Notes: April 3, 1952
  - Item 2: See What Your Library is Doing for Labor Groups, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Author: Boston Public Library
  - Item 3: Boston Public Library Books Available at the Walworth Library, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Notes: March 28, 1952
  - Item 4: Labor Management Social Work Institute, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Notes: Feb. 9, 1952
  - Item 5: Boston Public Library, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 6: Boston Public Library, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Notes: April 1952
  - Item 7: A Selected Booklist for the Ninth Annual Institute of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 8: Selected List of Books on Labor's Ecnomic Problems in Mobilizing for World Peace, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Item 9: Labor's Role in the Community, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Box: 2, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Tuition Remission Plan-Staff Members and Administration, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
    Author: Boston University
    Notes: Feb
  - Item 2: Tuition Remission Plan-Faculty, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Box: 2, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: The Labor Management School at Botany Beats Grievances, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Author: Botany Mills
- Box: 2, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Author: Bowery Savings Bank Co.
- Box: 2, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: You and the Bowman Dairy Company, Publication (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Author: Bowman Dairy Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Employees' Mutual Benefit Association Constitution, 1918; Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Author: S.F. Bowser and Co., Inc.
    Notes: Amended May 16, 1918
  - Item 2: The Bowser Plan of Shop Control by Joint Representation, 1919; Publication (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Box: 2, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Brewer Dry Dock Co. and Brewer Dry Dock Employees' Assn., Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Author: Brewer Dry Dock Co.
    Notes: Dec. 20 1946-Aug. 2, 1947
  - Item 2: Agreement between Brewer Dry Dock Co. and the Brewer Dry Dock Employees' Association, Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Notes: Aug. 2, 1947- Aug. 2, 1948
- Box: 2, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Industrial Manual, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Author: Bridgeport Brass Co.
  - Item 2: You and Your Job at Bridgeport Brass Co., 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Box: 2, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: The Way the Workers Like It, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Author: Lawrence Galton
  - Item 2: Victory Begins at Home, Publication (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Item 3: 2 Years of Teamwork, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Box: 2, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: The Future of American Labor-Management Relarions, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Author: Herman W. Steinkraus
- Box: 2, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Shop Rules and Regulations Applicable to Employees, 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Author: Brightwater Paper Co.
- Box: 2, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Your Job at Bristol Laboratories, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Author: Bristol Laboratories
- Box: 2, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: History of British Columbia Dept. of Labour, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Author: British Columbia Dept. of Labour
  - Item 2: Your Money Down the Drain, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 3: Summary of Proceedings, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Notes: Nov. 3-Nov. 7
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 5: Oct. 14 Out to Fight Controls!: Some questions and answers about Labour's National Day of Protest, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 6: This is Where We Stand on Canadian Autonomy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 7: This is Where We Stand on Strikes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 8: This is Where We Stand on Housing, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 9: This is Where We Stand Against Racism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 10: This is Where We Stand on the Rights of Working Women, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 11: This is Where We Stand on Pollution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 12: This is Where We Stand on Boycotts, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 13: This is Where We Stand on Picket Lines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 14: This is Where We Stand on Picket Lines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 15: This is Where We Stand on Day Care, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 16: This is Where We Stand on Public Ownership, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 17: This is Where We Stand on Unemployment, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 18: This is Where We Stand on the Cost of Living, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 19: This is Who We AreThe Federation, Voice of 200,000 British Columbians, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 20: Your Rights, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Notes: July 1, 1976
  - Item 21: Labour's Voice: The B.C. Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 22: Policy Statement-Defence Fund, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 23: Policy Statement Hot Declaration, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 24: Policy Statement Picketing, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Item 25: Provincial Finances: Setting B.C.s' Record Straight, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Notes: 2 cpoies
  - Item 26: I.C.B.C. The Real Dollars and Sense Story, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Notes: 3 copies
  - Item 27: Wage Controls: Another Attack on Working People and Their Families, Publication (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Notes: 2 copies
- Box: 2, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Twenty Years of Service to Music, 1960; Publication (Box 2, Folder 65)
    Author: Broadcast Music Inc.
- Box: 2, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: The Brookings Bulletin, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 66)
    Author: The Brookings Institution
    Notes: Vol. 14, No. 3 Fall
- Box: 2, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1916-1918 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    Author: Brooklyn Rapid Transit Company
- Box: 2, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1964; Publication (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Author: Brooklyn Technical High School
- Box: 2, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 2, Folder 69)